http://gelcandlecompany.com/privacy.html

Hem
Shrinivas Sugan..
The Gel Candle ..
About Us
Welcome to our Store!
Our candles are made with clean mineral oil which gives you the longest burn, a realistic scent and the cleanest burning experience you can find today! In small bathces we hand pour and very carefully assemble Forever Candles which are unique refillable designs. Available in scented and unscented gel candles in 90 hour Classic Jars, 30 hour Votives, 8 hour Tea Lights, Gel Melts(tm) for warmers, premium fragrance oils, incense, teas, and more.
Customer Service
Shipping
We use United States Postal Service and Fed-Ex Ground for shipping in the USA.
When your order ships we will notify you with tracking information.
Shop with Confidence
You can purchase from us with 100% Confidence. Payment is 100% secure and no card informaion is stored.
Available payment methods:
Information
Customer Service
About Us
Log In
Create Account
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Notice
Conditions of Use
Categories
Gel CandlesGel Melts™Diffusers for CarsJewelry DiffusersAroma WarmersWarmer AccessoriesColor Changing DiffusersOilsGoat Milk SoapIncense & SageWholesaleSpecials ...Featured Products ...All Products ...
Newest  [more]
Brown Glass Touch Activation Warmer DiffuserRetail Price: $14.95You save: $2.00  (13%)Our Price: $12.95
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order,
subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When ordering
or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your:
name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information.
You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following
ways:
• To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better
respond to your individual needs)
• To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website
offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
• To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively
respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
• To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred,
or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent,
other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service
requested.
• To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you
information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional
company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your
personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your
personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information
is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into
our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized
with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information
confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security
numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers
to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables
the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture
and remember certain information
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart
and understand and save your preferences for future visits.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie
is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings.
Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not
function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally
identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist
us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long
as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release
your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law,
enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to
other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be
in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore
will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your
consent.
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site
may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account
through the online shopping system. Once logged in click on the "My Account"
link on the top of the page to edit your information.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy
Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years
of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are
at least 13 years old or older.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this
page.
Small Cup Scented Gel Melts™ for...Retail Price: $1.50You save: $0.15  (10%)Our Price: $1.35  $1.29Save: 4% off
42 Unscented Gel Candle Tea Lights...$31.63
Bamboo Scented Gel Candle 90 Hour...Retail Price: $11.95You save: $1.00  (8%)Our Price: $10.95
Gel Candle Votive - unscented buy...Retail Price: $4.95You save: $1.00  (20%)Our Price: $3.95
4 Unscented Gel Candle Tea Lights...Retail Price: $4.50You save: $0.55  (12%)Our Price: $3.95
Reviews  [more]
I've been buying these candles now for the past 2 years - I...
Featured  [more]
Man Cave 90 Hour Gel Candle Classic JarRetail Price: $11.95You save: $1.00  (8%)Our Price: $10.95
Specials  [more]
Large Glass Wavy Edges Glass Dish For Oil WarmersRetail Price: $2.95You save: $0.45  (15%)Our Price: $2.50  $1.95Save: 22% off
Copyright © 2020 The Gel Candle Company.
Powered by Zen Cart.
Mobile Friendly Zen cart templates by Picaflor Azul.
Site Map
Privacy Notice
Conditions of Use
